OFORI-BOADU FREDERICK OSEI NANA

#19 Ashanti Lane, Okpoi Gonno

P.O Box CT 571

(+233)50 0025803

(+233)24 6789303

friedosei@gmail.com



Profile

I'm a creative and technical IT personnel who has studied IT and with some working experience, has a very strong desire to improve my networking knowledge to help manage your networking systems and frameworks. I also have some expertise in web designing and also currently building upon my skills in Multimedia and Graphic designing. With my determination to always improve upon what is available and constant zeal to seek knowledge, I believe I will be a great addition to any company and team.

Experience

Head, Tech Team, IESO Agribusiness Consult - January 2021- current Led the tech team in projects, Front End Development, Mobile Development, UI/UX design, IT consultancy and IT Networking Administration

Front End, and UI/UX Developer, IESO Agribusiness Consult - November 2019-January 2021

I worked on the development of Web Applications, Mobile Applications, UI/UX design, IT consultancy.

Data Center Engineer, National Information and Technology Agency (NITA)—September 2018 - September 2019

As a National Service Personnel for NITA, I worked as engineer for the National Data Center which is currently the biggest in Ghana. I monitored all systems in the Data Centre and Troubleshooted problems when they occurred, I also performed basic fiber optic connections to some of our systems.

Intern, Premium Technologies Ghana- June 2017-September 2017

As an intern, I was made to assist workers in the field, learnt and made link budgets for companies, how to work and establish links between wireless radios and also performed basic troubleshooting for clients of the company. Some of their clients were Tigo Ghana, Road safety commission of Ghana, BIMA.

Organizing Secretary, Computer Science Students Association of University Of Ghana – 2017-2018

I organized programs such as Seminars, Workshops, and fun activities such as and Python training program (in collaboration with Global Labs), Graphic Design Seminar, App deployment Workshop and many other outstanding projects. All these were accomplished with the help of my executives through our teamwork and resilient attitudes.

Education Zepto training school,

Software Engineering and Web design and Management- June 2014- September 2014

University of Ghana, Legon

BSc(Hons) Information Technology-2014-2018

Certified Ghana,

CCNA(routing and switching) training- February 2019- May 2019

Udemy,

React and Redux Development, React Native

Skills UX/UI Design

Web Application Development Mobile App Development

Networking Architecture And Design

Network Management

Microsoft Office

Sound and Video Editing

Photoshop

Certifications Cisco Certified Network Associate (Routing and Switching)

IBM Mobile Application Developer IBM Application Security Analyst React and Redux Developer (Udemy)

References Available on request

Repository https://github.com/FrederickOB